<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<document url="http://java-build.wvrgroup.internal:/opt/sites/perf4j-${project.version}/releases.html">
    <properties>
        <title>Release Notes</title>
    </properties>

    <body>
        <section name="Release 0.9.6 (1/4/09)">
            <ol>
                <li>Allow JMX notifications to be send when statistics attribute values exceed thresholds.</li>
                <li>Allow users to specify a logging level on the Profiled annotation.</li>
            </ol>
        </section>
        <section name="Release 0.9.5 (1/2/09)">
            <ol>
                <li>Added maven dependencies example to downloads page.</li>
                <li>Fixed bug where if timespans are very large, AsyncCoalescingStatisticsAppender can have large memory growth.</li>
                <li>Added Spring AOP section in developer guide.</li>
                <li>Changed build to create log4j-only and java.util.logging-only jars in the build for use with AspectJ compiler.</li>
            </ol>
        </section>
        <section name="Release 0.9.4 (12/31/08)">
            <ol>
                <li>Added performance graphs and graphing servlet.</li>
                <li>Added developer guide.</li>
                <li>Fixed a bug with the Profiled annotation where Jexl expressions would not be processed in
                    the message field unless the tag also had an expresison.  Now, Perf4J supports expressions in
                    the message AND/OR the tag.</li>
            </ol>
        </section>
        <section name="Release 0.9.3 (12/04/08)">
            <ol>
                <li>Fixed the AbstractTimingAspect's pointcut definition on doPerfLogging() to be more specific,
                    preventing duplicate log statements in some cases.</li>
                <li>Changed AOP tests to use AspectJ directly instead of Spring AOP since this is the recommended
                    integration.</li>
            </ol>
        </section>
        <section name="Release 0.9.2 (10/20/08)">
            <ol>
                <li>Made the LogParser log Exceptions and return System.exit.</li>
            </ol>
        </section>
        <section name="Release 0.9.1 (10/20/08)">
            <ol>
                <li>Decided it made more sense to make el() true by default.</li>
                <li>Added aspect support for timing.</li>
                <li>Refactored StatsValueRetriever in anticipation of Chart implementation.</li>
                <li>Added JMX support to Perf4J, replaced cobertura with emma.</li>
                <li>Changed how the async appender works to use the StopWatchLogIterator and GroupingStatisticsIterator
                    allowing reuse of these iterators in lots of places.</li>
            </ol>
        </section>
        <section name="Release 0.9 (10/20/08)">
            <ol>
                <li>Initial release of perf4J</li>
            </ol>
        </section>
    </body>
</document>








                 
